A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
Library of Virginia
- Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981). (Box 1-35.)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 157 (SJR 157): Identification of Problems in Youth (Referral Forms), 1979. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 158 (SJR 158): Establishment of Treatment Programs for Incarcerated Sex Offenders, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 159 (SJR 159): Juvenile Court-Public School Task Force, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Senate Resolution 124 (SR 124): Texas Study on Community Based Programs, 1978. (Box 23)
  - Sentence Reduction Considerations Relating to New Marijuana Laws, 1979-1981. (Box 26)
  - Sentry System, 1977. (Box 22)
  - Service Charges: Local, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Shalom et Benedictus, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Sheriffs' Management Conference, 1978. (Box 22)
  - Slayton, Del. Frank: General, 1978-1981. (Box 28)
  - Smith, H. Selwyn, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Southern Governors' Conference, 1976-1980. (Box 28)
  - Southern Governors' Conference Task Force Committee on Correctional Problems, 1976. (Box 22)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board: Raising a New Generation in the South (Preliminary Report), 1980. (Box 22)
  - Southern Legislative Conference, 1977-1980. (Box 28)
  - Southwestern Legislative Tour, 1978. (Box 22)
  - Southwestern State Hospital [empty folder], undated. (Box 8)
  - Special Clemency [empty folder], undated. (Box 22)
  - Speeches: Bell, Bill, 1977. (Box 13)
  - Speeches: Bell, E.W., III, 1978. (Box 13)
  - Speeches: Layman, T. Rodman, 1976-1981. (Box 1)
  - Speeches: Miscellaneous Individuals, 1978. (Box 13)
  - Speed Limit: Letters from Citizens, 1975-1979. (Box 4)
  - Speed Limit: Letters from Citizens (Pro and Con, and RE: Violations), 1976-1979. (Box 4)
  - Staggered Work Hours, 1978-1979. (Box 28)
  - Standardization of Agency Regulations, 1981. (Box 23)
  - State Agencies: Other (Agriculture and Commerce Data Processing), 1976. (Box 32)
  - State Agencies: Other (Auditor of Public Accounts), 1977. (Box 32)
  - State Agencies' Sub-State Districts and Regional Planning Areas, 1977. (Box 30)
  - State Aid to Localities, 1979. (Box 2)
  - State Bar, 1976-1977. (Box 32)
  - State Bar: Budget, 1977. (Box 32)
  - State Bar: Grant, 1976-1978. (Box 32)
  - State Bar: VALID Project, 1978. (Box 32)
  - State Fair Coordinating Committee, 1977-1981. (Box 22)
  - State Fire Chiefs Association of Virginia, undated. (Box 22)
  - State Government: General, 1974-1980. (Box 32)
  - State Police [2 folders], 1976-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: 6135 Equipment Replacement, 1974-1977. (Box 32)
  - State Police: Acquisition of Tazewell Property, 1978-1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Acquisition of Tazewell Property, 1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Administrative Conference, 1978-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Air Pollution Emission Inspection Program, 1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Annual Vehicle Inspection Position Paper, 1981. (Box 21)
  - State Police: Area 30 Office (Norton), 1979-1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Badges and Patches, 1976-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Basic Communications System Work Plan, 1979-1980. (Box 5)
  - State Police: Blue Lights, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Cattle Thefts, 1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: CB Radios, 1977-1979. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Cigarette Smuggling, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Communications (Federal Communications Commission), 1979-1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Complaint (Trooper Clark's Wife), 1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Correspondence, 1977-1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Data Processing, 1976-1981. (Box 32)
  - State Police: Division Boundaries/Reorganization, 1978-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Fingerprint System, 1978-1979. (Box 35)
  - State Police: First Division Headquarters, 1976-1980. (Box 26)
  - State Police: Fourth Division Headquarters, 1977-1979. (Box 26)
  - State Police: Floyd County Additional Trooper Requests, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Fredericksburg Request for More Troopers, 1977. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Fugitive Warrant (R.E. Davis), 1976-1977. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Gasoline Monitoring, 1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: General, 1976-1978. (Box 32)
  - State Police: General [2 folders], 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: General [3 folders], 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: General, 1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Guns, 1978-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Investigation, Div. of, 1974-1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Investigation, Div. of, 1979-1981. (Box 22)
  - State Police: Investigation, Div. of, (General), 1979-1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Investigation, Div. of, (Reorganization), 1979. (Box 22)
  - State Police: Investigations (Albemarle Sheriff's Office), 1977. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Buchanan County), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Campbell County), 1977. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Caroline County Commonwealth's Attorney, J. J. Ambler), 1977. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Carroll County), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Charles City County, Sheriff White), 1977. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Christian, H.E., Death of), 1977-1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Investigations (Commerce, Department of), 1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Investigations (Cole, Michael E., Death of), 1978-1981. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Corrections' Fraud), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Craig County), undated. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Dalton, Ronnie), 1973-1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Dickenson, Alfred B., Jr.), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Dinwiddie County Sheriff's Office), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Drugs), 1977-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Investigations (Electronics Subcontract), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Elkton, Town of, Drugs), 1977-1978. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Ely, Dennis R.), 1976-1977. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Energy, Department of), 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Energy Office), 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Fairfax Sheriff), 1977-1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Floyd County, Sheriff George E. Branscome), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (General Correspondence), 1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Investigations (General Services, Dept. of, Div. of Purchases and Supply) [2 folders], 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Giles County), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Governor's Mansion), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Health, Dept. of, R.O. Perry and D. Ham), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Hefner v. Clark, RE: Land Transactions), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Henry County), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Highway Department, Bristol), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Lee County), 1976-1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (McGlothlin, Jim, United Coal Company), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Moccasin Valley), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Monaco, Barbara J., Disappearance of), 1978-1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Montgomery County Sheriff's Dept.), 1976-1977. (Box 7)
  - State Police: Investigations (Obenshain Crash), 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Patrick County Sheriff's Office), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Pittsylvania Investigation, Mr. Whitehead), 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Port Authority), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Portsmouth Officials), 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Investigations (Purchases and Supply, Dept. of) [2 folders], 1975-1978. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Investigations (Rejected by Attorney General's Office), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Rockbridge County Sheriff's Office), 1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Sheriff T.E. McGregor and Commonwealth's Attorney G.A. Jones), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Smyth County, Parker, Gale, Death of), 1977. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Smyth County, Request by Special Grand Jury), 1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (State Bar Request, Mr. Whitehead), 1978. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (State Penitentiary), 1978. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Surry County Treasurer's Office), 1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Tazewell Correctional Unit #31), 1980. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Tompkins, Willis, Dept. of Highways and Transportation), 1980. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (VCU-MCV), 1979-1980. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Beach Jail), 1978. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Beach Sheriff), 1977-1978. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Employment Commission), 1981. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Medical Assistance Program and Nursing Home), 1980. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Museum of Fine Arts), 1979. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Virginia Parole Board), 1978. (Box 13)
  - State Police: Investigations (Warren County), 1977. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Investigations (Wise County), 1977. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Marked/Unmarked Cars, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Minority Employment, 1974-1978. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Minority Recruiting, 1971-1977. (Box 35)
  - State Police: New Division in Augusta County, 1978. (Box 26)
  - State Police: News Releases and Newsletters, 1978-1981. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Nonresident Violators Compact, 1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Norton Office, 1979. (Box 26)
  - State Police: Organized Crime, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Policeman's Bill of Rights, 1978. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Position Paper (Annual Motor Vehicle Inspection), 1981. (Box 31)
  - State Police: Procedures for Handling Requests by the Governor's Office for Investigations, 1977. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Progress Reports of the Uniform Accident Prevention and Safety Program, 1975-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Public Safety Officers Benefits Act, 1977. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Radar Dectection Devices [2 folders], 1977. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Radar Equipment, 1978-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Radar Unit Policy, 1977. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Radio Communications System, 1980-1981. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Red Lights, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Re-employment Policy, 1977-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Replacement of Processor, 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Resident Trooper Program, 1978-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Salaries, 1979. (Box 26)
  - State Police: Salary Differentials, 1977-1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Saturation Patrols, 1977-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: SEAWALL and TALON Operations (Fencing), 1977-1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Selective Enforcement Program, 1979. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Speeding Violation Arrests, 1976-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: State Police Communications System [2 folders], 1976-1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Statewide Interdepartmental Radio System (SIRS), 1977-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Superintendent Vacancy, 1977-1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Take Home Pay, 1977. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Tazewell County Law Enforcement Facilities (Southwest Virginia Community College), 1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Thomas, Mrs. M.K. (RE: Complaint, Mrs. Dorothea Cox), 1979. (Box 14)
  - State Police: Training Academy, 1980. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Training School Addition, 1978-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Trooper Assignments, 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Trooper Entrance Requirements and Test Battery, 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Trooper Strength (Orange County), 1979. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Trooper Strength (Salem, Bath and Highland Counties), 1978. (Box 11)
  - State Police: Troopers (Cohen, E.A.), 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Conner, J.S.), 1976. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Dyer, R.F.), 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Fisher, G.W., Jr.), 1976-1977. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Honaker, Gerald L.), 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Lohr, Robert), 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Messinger, O.W.), 1977-1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Petska, Cheryl L.), 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Price, C.S.), 1977-1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Sexton, K.D.), 1976-1977. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Smith, Darrell K.), 1976-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Troopers (Spangler, Michael D.), 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Uniform Traffic Summons, 1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: U.S. Case, 1978. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Vehicle Inspections, 1978-1981. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Vehicles, 1978-1979. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Vehicles (Purchase of and Assignment), 1980. (Box 35)
  - State Police: Virginia Beach Discrimination Suit, 1977. (Box 16)
  - State Police: Warrenton (State Police Headquarters, Warrenton and Fauquier), 1977-1980. (Box 15)
  - State Police: Winchester Area Office, 1979. (Box 15)
  - State Training Advisory Committee, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Status of Women, 1976. (Box 22)
  - Staunton Correctional Center, 1976-1981. (Box 8)
  - Staunton Correctional Center: Investigation of Allegations, 1980. (Box 8)
  - Strike: Bland Center, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Strike: State Penitentiary, 1977. (Box 25)
  - Strikes, 1978-1979. (Box 22)
  - Supreme Court: Data Processing, 1974-1979. (Box 32)
  - Supreme Court: General, 1976-1980. (Box 32)
  - Surety Bonds, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Surplus Property: Equipment and Furnishings, 1977-1980. (Box 28)
  - Surplus Property: Notices, State-Owned, 1975-1979. (Box 28)
  - Temporary Loans Outstanding, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Tidewater Detention Home, 1978-1980. (Box 31)
  - Title XX Funds, 1976-1979. (Box 28)
  - Toll Passes, 1977. (Box 27)
  - Transportation Safety, Dept. of (formerly Highway Safety Division), 1977-1980. (Box 22)
  - Tractorcade, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Transportation: General, 1978-1980. (Box 28)
  - Truckers' Strike, 1979. (Box 22)
  - Unemployment Compensation Act, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Uniform Crime Reports [empty folder], undated. (Box 32)
  - Uniform State Laws: National Conference, 1979. (Box 28)
  - UNIVAC, 1978. (Box 27)
  - UNIVAC: 9480 Replacement, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Urban Crime Policy: Federal, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Urban Policy Status Reports, 1978-1979. (Box 27)
  - VALC Committee Studying Youthful Offenders, 1977-1978. (Box 27)
  - VALID Project, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Virginia Association of Commonwealth's Attorneys, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Virginia Coalition for Delinquency Prevention (GR 10-10), 1976-1979. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Commission for Children and Youth Needs Assessment Documents, 1977. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Correctional Center for Women, 1976-1978. (Box 8)
  - Virginia Crime Prevention Association, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, 1976-1977. (Box 27)
  - Virginia Juvenile Officers Association, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Virginia Liaison Office: Stan Parris, 1978-1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Parole Board, 1976-1979. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Sheriffs' Association, 1976-1980. (Box 28)
  - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1976-1979. (Box 27)
  - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education: Study of Local Advisory Councils on Vocational Education, 1979. (Box 27)
  - Virginia State Law Database Project, 1976. (Box 5)
  - Volunteerism, 1977-1981. (Box 14)
  - Watimka Halfway House, 1976-1978. (Box 8)
  - Welfare, Dept. of: Information and Referral Program, 1978. (Box 27)
  - Word Processing Manual (MASD): Administrative and Financial Directive 11, 1978-1979. (Box 32)
  - Year-End Statements, 1976-1979. (Box 24)
  - Youth Populations, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: 72-Hour Detention of Children (A.G.'s Opinion), 1978. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: Capital Improvements, 1977-1978. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: Carpenter, K., 1976. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: Planning Documents, undated. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: Taylor, L.P., 1977. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services, Div. of: VALC Committee's Study of Services to Youthful Offenders, 1977. (Box 31)
  - Youth Services: Evaluation of by Appropriations Committee (Verditz), 1977. (Box 26)
  - Zero-Base Budgeting, 1977-1978. (Box 6)